<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayman Lafaz</title>
    <link>https://aymanlafaz.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ayman Lafaz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2023, Ayman Lafaz</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aymanlafaz.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI is not really open</title>
      <link>https://aymanlafaz.com/post/openai-is-not-really-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aymanlafaz.com/post/openai-is-not-really-open/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are we on the verge of a new AI revolution?</title>
      <link>https://aymanlafaz.com/post/are-we-on-the-verge-of-a-new-ai-revolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aymanlafaz.com/post/are-we-on-the-verge-of-a-new-ai-revolution/</guid>
      <description>You may be tempted to think that with the new media buzz about all the new and exciting AI models coming up like (GPT-3, Stable Diffusion, DALLE-2, &amp;hellip;), that we are on a verge of a breakthrough with the ever so talked about AGI (Artificial General Intelligence) which have been portrayed by movies where AI takes over and enslaves humanity and all that kind of stuff. but still the current progress is still far from it in my opinion, and not to downplay the impact these kinds of developments have on society at large because indeed this progress that was achieved will change the way things are done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPT models are not as good as you think</title>
      <link>https://aymanlafaz.com/post/gpt-models-are-not-as-good-as-you-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aymanlafaz.com/post/gpt-models-are-not-as-good-as-you-think/</guid>
      <description>With the introduction of ChatGPT alot of people who would have never heard about the advancements in Text Generation models now are more aware of it, lots of people now are using these models to take care of the hassle of having to write stuff as we all can admit that writing is not fun.
But I think that these models are far from good as I will explain now, ChatGPT which is just a GPT-3 model with the capacity to have dialogue can be very overly confident even when spewing the most made-up and unfactual responses you can imagine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://aymanlafaz.com/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aymanlafaz.com/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://aymanlafaz.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aymanlafaz.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me I’m Ayman Lafaz Machine Learning Engineer, I’ve worked on many Machine learning and Data Science projects especially in time series forecasting, data analytics and visualization and computer vision, I’m always looking for new opportunities to share and expand my skills also as a freelancer.
Experience Data Science and Machine Learning Freelancer | December 2021 - March 2023
Working with clients on various data and machine learning related projects, taking a data driven approach to solve challenging business problems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
